(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-05T14:33:51.413694",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ふまっくす ふるす！！ FUBUNKINGDOM STORY SIDE ROOM
Fubumaccs Fulls!! Fubukingdom Story Side Room
#ふぉっくすろーむ
#Pokingoon
かわいい！絶対にかわいい！
Cute! Absolutely cute!
もっと甘やかして？
Spoil me even more?
頑張る理由は私でしょ？
The reason you work hard is me, right?
何してもかわいいんだもん
Whatever I do, I'm just so cute.
今日も完璧な自分に酔っちゃおう
Let's get intoxicated by my perfection today too!
もっとドキドキしてね
Get your heart racing even more,
もっと夢中になって
and become totally obsessed with me.
キミに褒められるたびかわいくなる
Every time you praise me, I get cuter.
ふわふわとろとろ頭の中私だけ
Fluffy and melting, my head is full of just you.
好きをお届けいいことづくめ
Delivering my love, it's all good things.
独占してね
Monopolize me, okay?
きゅんきゅんきゅん！
Kyun kyun kyun!
あざとかわいい 大人かわいい
Cunningly cute, maturely cute.
変幻自在 かわいい！
Ever-changing, cute!
一生一緒だよねキミにだけ萌え萌えきゅん
Together forever, right? Moe moe kyun just for you!
朝もかわいい夜もかわいい毎分毎秒かわいい
Cute in the morning, cute at night, cute every minute and second.
全部がすきでしょ生まれつきの才能
You love all of it, right? It's innate talent.
ラブリー属性 ♡ ちゅっ！
Lovely attribute ♡ Chu!
目が離せなくなっちゃうでしょ？
You can't take your eyes off me, right?
世界にひとりだけだもん
I'm the only one in the world.
注がれた愛の分だけ無敵になる
I become invincible by the amount of poured love.
世界一あいりんちゅ 宇宙一あいりんちゅ
The world's #1 airinchu, the universe's #1 airinchu!
あまあまな私って大好きでしょ？
You love sweet-as-sugar me, right?
おバカかわいい 天然かわいい
Ditzily cute, naturally cute.
困るくらいかわいい
So cute it's troubling.
まだまだ好きにさせちゃう
I'll make you fall for me even more.
キミにだけらぶらぶちゅっ
Love love chu just for you.
オンもかわいい オフもかわいい
Cute on, cute off,
年中無休かわいい！
Cute 365 days a year!
何回言っても足りないんだからかわいい！
No matter how many times I say it, it's not enough, so cute!
言いたいことがあるんだよ
There's something I want to say!
やっぱりフブキはかわいいよ！
As expected, Fubuki is cute!
好き好き大好きやっぱ好き やっと見つけたお姫様
Love love super love, still love. The princess I finally found.
俺が生まれてきた理由は それはフブキに出会うため
The reason I was born is to meet Fubuki.
俺と一緒に人生歩もう
Let's walk through life together.
世界で1番愛してる 愛してる
I love you more than anyone in the world, I love you.
でもねでもね君がいないと始まないんだよ
But you know, without you it wouldn't even start.
ずっとずっと私の隣にいてね
Stay by my side forever and ever, okay?
あざとかわいい 大人かわいい
Cunningly cute, maturely cute.
変幻自在 かわいい！
Ever-changing, cute!
一生一緒だよね キミにだけ萌え萌えきゅん
Together forever, right? Moe moe kyun just for you.
朝もかわいい夜もかわいい 毎分毎秒かわいい
Cute in the morning, cute at night, cute every minute and second.
全部がすきでしょ 生まれつきの才能
You love all of it, right? It's innate talent.
愛される天才 ラブリー属性 ♡ ちゅっ！
A genius at being loved, lovely attribute ♡ Chu!
ライブ会場にお越しのスクワッドの皆さん！こんばんは！
Everyone in the squad here at the concert venue! Good evening!
ふわふわしっぽのご奉仕 あなたの心の一番星 白上フブキでーーす！
Serving you with my fluffy tail, your heart's brightest star, Shirakami Fubuki here!
ハイファイブー！本日は白上の生誕ライブにお越し下さり、誠にありがとうございます！
High five! Thank you so much for coming to Shirakami's birthday live today!
今日のライブのテーマはなんと！アイドル！アイドル力全開のフブキちゃんを皆さん最後まで目に焼き付けてくださいね！
The theme of today's live is... an idol! Please burn Fubuki-chan's full idol power into your eyes until the very end!
ということで、今回のハッシュタグ、#ふぉっくすろーむで
So, with the hashtag #Pokingoon...
あっそ!
Ah so!
ボスとして楽しんでくださいねー！
Please enjoy yourself as the boss!
ではでは次の曲もいってみましょー！
Well then, let's go for the next song too!
ねえねえ もしもものもしもだよ
Hey hey, what if—just what if—
私が帰り道 グリズリーに襲われたら
if I were attacked by a grizzly bear on my way home,
あなたならどうする？
what would you do?
もしももしもあなたならどうする？
What if, what if it were you, what would you do?
グリズリーに襲われたら♡
If attacked by a grizzly bear♡
もしもね 帰り道 グリズリーだって出くらして
If on my way home, I ran into a grizzly bear,
闇夜で目が合えば 恐怖で動けないわ
and our eyes met in the dark, I'd be too terrified to move.
震える唇で 助けてと言ったら
With trembling lips, if I called out for help,
あなたはすぐに来てくれますか？
would you come running right away?
ねぇ 嘘ついて あしらわないで 真実なの お願い！
Hey, don't lie, don't brush me off, tell me the truth, please!
パジャマだって 駆けつけてね
Come running even in your pajamas,
1秒を争うのよ
we're fighting over every single second.
私服に着替える間に 骨まで食べられちゃうわ
By the time you change into casual clothes, I'll be eaten down to the bones!
裸足だって 駆けつけてね
Come running even barefoot,
私を疑う前に
before you doubt me.
心配でたまらなくて 走り出してほしいのです
You're so worried you can't help it, I want you to run out.
そんな人が嬉しいの
That kind of person makes me happy.
もしもね 曲がり角 グリズリーにぶつかり
If at a street corner, I bumped into a grizzly bear,
物陰で向き合えば 怖くて叫べないわ
and faced it from the shadows, I'd be too scared to scream.
怯える左手で 助けてと止めるしたら
With a trembling left hand, if I cried out for help,
あなたはすぐに見に来てくれますか？
would you come to see me right away?
ねぇ ほら震えて 片付けないで 本当そんなの信じて
Hey, don't tremble, don't tidy up, really, believe that!
仕事だって 駆けつけてね
Come running even from work,
何もかもを投げ出して
throwing everything else aside.
残業が終わるまでに ほら丸飲みされちゃうわ
By the time overtime ends, I'll be swallowed whole!
どこにだって 駆けつけてね
Come running no matter where you are,
私を疑う前に
before you doubt me.
いても立ってもいられない 取り乱してほしいのです
You can't sit still, I want you to lose your composure.
そんな人が愛しいの
That kind of person is so dear to me.
ねぇ もしもし 大変大変 帰り道にグリズリーがいるの！
Hey, hello? It's an emergency! There's a grizzly on my way home!
助けて 私怖くて 一歩も動けないよ
Help me, I'm so scared I can't even move a step!
今すぐ来て 助けて！
Come right now, help me!
きゃー ここに来るよ 私のこと見てる！
KYAA! It's coming over here, it's looking at me!
いやぁ！ 助けてよ！
Nooo! Help me!
ねぇ 嘘ついて あしらわないで 真実なの
Hey, don't lie, don't brush me off, it's the truth—
お願い おねえがい！
Please, pleeease!
パジャマだって 駆けつけてね
Come running even in your pajamas,
1秒を争うのよ
we're fighting over every single second.
私服に着替える間に 骨まで食べられちゃうわ
By the time you change into casual clothes, I'll be eaten down to the bones!
裸足だって 駆けつけてね
Come running even barefoot,
私を疑う前に
before you doubt me.
心配でたまらなくて 走り出してほしいのです
You're so worried you can't help it, I want you to run out.
そんな人が嬉しいの
That kind of person makes me happy.
あなたしかいないの
There's nobody else but you.
Special♡Spell
メトロで揺られる帰り道 また今日も寝坊したい
A commute shaken by the metro, I want to oversleep again today.
意味ないそんなの分かってるもん
I know that's meaningless, but still...
踊って ドキドキ君が浮かんだディスプレイ
Dancing, my heart flutters, a display with you in mind—
一瞬笑顔へとアップデート
updating instantly to a smile.
横切るきらめく風が どんなときだって正解
The glittering breeze passing by is always right, no matter what.
好きだけ集めて コトコト煮込んだママレイド
Gathering only what I love, marmalade simmered down slowly—
溢れた涙もスパイスにしよう
let's turn overflowing tears into spice too.
甘くて苦いは私のすべて 君に教えてほしいの
Sweet and bitter is my everything; I want you to teach me about it.
シークレットタイム 答えは一つじゃ
Secret time—is the answer just one?
エジャム付いてる 可愛いでしょう？
Jam-packed and cute, right?
くるりとなえて 秘密の呪文 スペシャルな魔法
Chant it around, a secret spell, a special magic!
ピンクみたいにスウィーティー 恋は禁断の罪の味
Sweet like pink, love is the taste of forbidden sin.
叶えて奇跡を注文 スペシャルは希望
Grant it, order a miracle; special is hope!
わがままくらいでいいんです 女のコだもん
Being a bit selfish is fine, since I'm a girl!
なめてもいいよ？
Is it okay to taste it?
いつも心配ばっか 可愛いかせいで 適当に適当に生きてこ
Always worrying so much, earning cuteness—let's live casually!
自分の機嫌をとるのも自分です
Taking care of your own mood is up to you too.
まあ もっとほめちょうだいってば！
Well, praise me more, come on!
なんて悩んでても 結局君の一言が全部
No matter how much I fret, in the end, a single word from you
あっさり解決しちゃうから
resolves everything so easily!
なんかちょっとかなり ずるくて不満でしょ
Isn't it a bit too cunning and frustrating?
ぐるぐるネガティブの請求 いろいろストレスの20
Spinning invoice of negativity, all kinds of stress multiplied by twenty!
ドキドキときめき I want you
Palpitating, fluttering, I want you!
いつでも君だけ I love you 誓いの紐は忘れないで
Always only you, I love you—don't forget the cord of vows!
スペシャルな魔法 最後のハッピーエンドへ
Special magic, to the final happy ending!
ふさわしいヒロインは誰？ 私でしょ？
Who is the fitting heroine? It's me, right?
くるりとなえて 秘密の呪文 スペシャルな魔法
Chant it around, a secret spell, a special magic!
ピンクみたいにスウィーティー 恋は禁断の罪の味
Sweet like pink, love is the taste of forbidden sin.
叶えて奇跡を注文 世界一スペシャルな希望
Grant it, order a miracle; the world's most special hope!
わがままくらいでいいんです 女のコだもん
Being a bit selfish is fine, since I'm a girl!
思うまま自由に 夢見るストーリー
Freely as you wish, a dream-filled story!
さあ 明日はどんな私になろう
Now, what kind of me will tomorrow bring?
魔法の呪文 隠し味はだめ？
A magic spell—is a secret ingredient not allowed?
教えてあげないの
I won't tell you!
エキジを90溶かしちゃって はじめメイドイン愛の迷宮
Melting the EQ to 90, first, the labyrinth of Made in Love!
くりてぃかる♡ぷりちー
Critical♡Pretty!
踵落として即睡眠 世界へ愛をばらまいちゃうの
A heel drop, then instant sleep—let's scatter love across the world!
待って待って 燃え尽きずいほー
Wait, wait, don't burn out just yet!
待って待って 褒めなきゃちょいほー
Wait, wait, if you don't praise me, I'll sulk!
ご主人様 お嬢様のこともどきっとさせて心を おそうじ
Making master and milady's hearts skip a beat, cleaning up their hearts!
待って待って 持ち時間15秒
Wait, wait, time limit: 15 seconds!
待って待って ビルドもたいど
Wait, wait, build your attitude!
毎日がんばってるもん 褒め出しでしょ
I work hard every day, so you should praise me!
もっと好かれ 見つかれ 目を離しちゃだめ
Fall in love with me more, gaze at me, don't take your eyes off me!
ざっと顔して はにゃはにゃ 君とはすでできゅんです あちゅまむちゅです
Making a playful face, hannya-hannya—with you, it's already "kyun"!
頭がぐるぐるで暗いシス
Head spinning, everything is dark and dizzy.
なかったてじゃないよ なんだったてしちょう
That wasn't it? What was it? Let's assert it!
ちゅうまわたいじゅはつぎ
My world is coming next, chu!
純粋に徐々に 君のために
Purely, gradually, for your sake!
準備着々 私のため
Preparations steady, for my sake!
エキジを90溶かしちゃって はじめメイドイン愛の迷宮
Melting the EQ to 90, first, the labyrinth of Made in Love!
くりてぃかる♡ぷりちー きゅんきゅんきゅんきゅん
Critical♡Pretty, kyun kyun kyun kyun!
考えられなくなっちゃって もうね寝るりじ
I can't think anymore, so time to sleep!
神交差点 つねに満点
Divine intersection, always a perfect score!
やばい見た目 甘すぎすぱいしきぜつしちゃうほど愛をあげるからね
Dangerously cute, overly sweet, spicy enough to make you faint!
少年のようじょう けなげだよね
A boy's innocent heart—it's so endearing, isn't it?
もっと優しく 優しく 手を繋いでいて
More gently, gently, holding hands together!
どうにもならない幻想も
Even impossible illusions,
あちこち行って恋せよ
go everywhere and fall in love!
脳内麻薬貞操も
Brain narcotics and chastity too,
臨界突破して
breaking through the limit!
しょうぼり駅前騒々も
The gloomy station square commotion too,
たちまちぴっとポイ捨て後
instantly tossed away with a snap.
結局装備どうする?
In the end, what about our gear?
そうHurry Hurry Up!!
Yeah, hurry, hurry up!
もう 無理できない!逃走の
I can't take it anymore! Flight's
足取り見ておいてよ
footsteps, watch and see.
ドンキで出来栄え上等の
High quality work from Donki,
カラコンばかりして
wearing colored contacts all the time.
コンプラ的にも炎上の
Compliance-wise, a flaming
泣きはらしたメイクで
makeup with swollen crying eyes.
結局逃避行する
In the end, we go on an escape journey,
もう針千本飲みます!!
swallowing a thousand needles now!!
麻痺をかけて
Cast a numbness,
ヤバい夢を見せて
show me a dangerous dream,
そんなスウィーティー賭けて
wagering that sweet thing,
探してをもっとレッツゴーです
searching for more, let's go!
愛してくれないから頑張れる
I can try hard because you don't love me,
二人回転成り立たあっとホーム
our rotation makes a heartwarming home.
どこかで飛ばせ最新トレンド
Blast the latest trend somewhere,
まだ足りなくも
still not enough,
もっと欲しくない私のごとくには
I don't want more, like in my place.
瞬き無くも
Without blinking either,
もっと欲しくない
I don't want more
私のところに
to my place.
置いて
Leave me behind,
君と遊びで生きてます
living life through play with you,
あっというま中継です
in the blink of an eye, it's a broadcast.
頭クラクラで暗い思考
Head spinning, gloomy thoughts,
なっちゃってんじゃないよ
don't become like that!
なんだったって主張を
Whatever the claim was,
ちょま私ピュア好き
wait, I love being pure!
純粋に 中々に 君のために
Purely, quite a bit, for your sake,
つまり 実質 私のため
meaning, essentially for my own sake.
エゴジオ急ジとけてちゃって星メインドイン愛のめい
Egoistic emergency, melting away, main star of love's melody.
フジオキュージとけちゃって星メインドイン愛のメイ
Emergency melting away, main star of love's melody.
クリティカルぷりちー きゅきゅきゅきゅ
Critical pretty, q-q-q-q!
焼き付けてこの繚乱の的高揚を
Burn it into your eyes, this dazzling, chaotic exaltation!
Wow...
太陽は知らない
The sun knows nothing,
月には届かない
it doesn't reach the moon.
絶望も希望も震える鼓動も
Despair and hope, and the trembling heartbeat too,
ざめく人ごみの纏わり付く温度
the clinging warmth of the rustling crowd—
今だけは心地よくなるの
only for now, it feels so comfortable.
遠雷に似た合図が響く
A signal resembling distant thunder echoes,
逸る想いと呼び合うように
as if calling out to impatient feelings.
感じさせてよ もっと愛を
Make me feel more love,
暗闇に咲く葛藤と
with the conflict blooming in the darkness,
見つめ合っていたい
wanting to gaze into each other's eyes.
沈黙を破って 降りそそぐたび
Breaking the silence, every time it rains down,
心 儚さに揺れて
the heart sways in transience.
鬱陶しいくらいの熱量に ああ もう少し
To an annoying amount of heat, ah, just a little more
浮かされていたいな
I want to be carried away by it.
息を呑んで そらさないで
Holding my breath, don't look away,
忘れたくない 繚乱の的高揚を
I don't want to forget this dazzling, chaotic exaltation!
Wow...
この先何年も 思い出すのでしょう
For how many years to come will I remember this?
らしくない君の 汗伝う横顔
Your unusual profile with sweat trickling down.
木漏れ日の下闇から覗く 裏腹な
Peeking from the shade of tree leaves, contradictory
眼差しは何を見ていたの?
gaze, what were you looking at?
星の軌跡を 夜風が溶かす
The night breeze melts the trajectory of the stars,
歌う心にくすぐるように
tickling my singing heart.
忘れさせてよ こんな憂いを
Make me forget such sorrow,
擦れた裸足の切なさも 気にならないくらい
enough that the pain of worn-out bare feet doesn't even matter.
お揃いで買った飴がけの宝石を
The candy-coated jewels we bought matching,
下で遊ばせて
letting them play on our tongues.
第三者目線じゃ 取るに足らない
From a third-party perspective, insignificant,
瞬間がたまらなく愛しいの
but that moment is unbearably precious.
終わらないで 明けるまで
Don't end, until dawn breaks,
トキメキと喧騒に溺れたい
I want to drown in excitement and commotion!
花の命はなんて言って 色に出にけり
What do they say a flower's life is? Showing in its color,
感情を諦めたくない
I don't want to give up on my emotions.
沈黙を破って あまのじゃくな瞳の
Breaking the silence, with eyes of a contrarian,
その奥に触れて
touching deep inside.
感じさせてよ もっと愛を
Make me feel more love,
暗闇に咲く葛藤と見つめ合っていたい
wanting to gaze into each other's eyes with the conflict blooming in the darkness.
もっと もっと
More and more,
暗闇に咲く葛藤と
with the conflicts blooming in the darkness,
見つめ合っていたい
I want to keep gazing into your eyes.
不意に訪れる
The sudden silence that visits,
引き足の静けさに 気づかないふりして
pretending not to notice the hesitant stillness.
鬱陶しいくらいの
With a passion so stifling,
熱量に もうもう少し浮かされていたいな
I want to stay swept up in it just a little longer.
息を呑んで 焼き付けて
Holding my breath, burning it into my heart,
忘れたくないような 繚乱の高揚を
that dazzling exaltation I never want to forget.
最高の最後まで 目を逸らさないで
Don't look away until the very end.
＋もしもしダーリン＋
[Song: +Moshimoshi Darling+]
もしもしキキ？
Hello Kiki?
もしもしラビ？
Hello Rabi?
もしもしキティ？
Hello Kitty?
ハートはStrawberry
My heart is strawberry.
もしもしマイダーリン
Hello, my darling.
この番号は ただいま恋の留守電中
This number is currently reaching love's voicemail.
ねぇキミは 知らないんでしょ？
Hey, you don't know that, do you?
女の子は 魔法で出来てる
Girls are made of magic.
好きなものは？
What do you like?
好きな人は？ （ヒミツだからね）
Who do you like? [It's a secret, though]
よそ見なんて出来ないくらい いつだってプリンセス
Always a princess, so much so that I can't look away anywhere else.
鏡鏡 ねぇもっと 光ってわたし映して
Mirror, mirror, shine brighter and reflect me!
過去の投稿にポチキリシ（だってもっと可愛い更新中っ）
Tapping on past posts [Because I'm updating my cuteness even more!]
ダーリン！
Darling!
イニシャルに付けた♡のマーク
The heart mark attached to your initials
こんなにキミが大好きなのは内緒です
is a secret—how much I love you so much.
コミコミ二人しか知らないチュチュチュなSweet talk
The chuchuchu sweet talk that only the two of us know.
あぁ神様の言う通りにはしない！
Ah, I won't do as God says!
もしもし聴こえる？
Hello, can you hear me?
もしもしI love you…
Hello, I love you...
もしもしマイダーリン
Hello, my darling
もしもしLove Rabbit
Hello, Love Rabbit
もしもしKiss Kitty ハートはStrawberry
Hello, Kiss Kitty, My heart is strawberry
もしもしマイダーリン この番号はただいま恋の留守電中
Hello, my darling. This number is currently reaching love's voicemail.
四六時中 なんだって構ってほしい！
24/7, I want you to pay attention to me no matter what!
積もるメッセージ 未読はタブー！
Piling messages—leaving them unread is taboo!
お決まりの大反省会（Every night routine）
The usual grand self-reflection meeting (Every night routine)
後悔しない！後悔しよう また病んじゃうじゃん
No regrets! Let's regret it. I'm gonna get sick of it again.
世界中をすべてピンク色に乗り換えて
Switch the whole world to all pink!
私の好き全肯定してね
Fully affirm everything I like
ずっと裏切る計画中っ
Always plotting to betray [you]!
ダーリン！早く見つけてよ 逢いたいのサイン
Darling! Find me quickly, it's a sign that I want to see you.
こんなにキミが鈍感なのは誤算です
It's a miscalculation that you're this dense.
コミコミお揃いのマイコで キュキュキュなSweet heart
The matching-mic chuchuchu sweet heart.
あぁハッピーエンドの続きなんていらない！
Ah, I don't need a continuation of a happy ending!
もしもし聴こえる？ もしもしI love you…
Hello, can you hear me? Hello, I love you...
むかしむかしあるところに お姫様がいました お姫様は言いました 誰かのために可愛くなるんじゃない わたしは私のために可愛くなるの
Once upon a time, in a far-off place, there was a princess. The princess said: 'I don't become cute for someone else's sake, I become cute for my own sake!'
むかしむかしあるところに お姫様がいました お姫様は言いました...
Once upon a time, in a far-off place...
プリンセス！唯一無二の物語を描くのは
Princess! Writing this one-and-only story...
誰？生まれ変わってもまた私になりたい！絶対に！
Who? Even if I'm reborn, I want to become myself again! Absolutely!
ダーリン！イニシャルに付けた♡のマーク
Darling! The heart mark attached to your initials
こんなにキミが大好きなのは秘密です
is a secret—how much I love you so much.
コミコミ二人しか知らないチュチュチュなSweet talk
The chuchuchu sweet talk that only the two of us know.
あぁ神様の言う通りにはしない！
Ah, I won't do as God says!
もしもし聴こえる？ もしもしI love you…
Hello, can you hear me? Hello, I love you...
もしもしマイダーリン もしもしLove Rabbit もしもしKiss Kitty ハートはStrawberry
Hello my darling, Hello Love Rabbit, Hello Kiss Kitty, My heart is strawberry.
もしもしマイダーリン この番号はただいま恋の留守電中 see you later…♡
Hello, my darling. This number is currently reaching love's voicemail... See you later...♡
ray
[Song: ray]
お疲れした のはもっと前のことだったような
It feels like we said our goodbyes long before that,
悲しい光は封じ込めて かかと擦り減らしたんだ
trapping the sorrowful light and wearing down my heels.
君といた時は見えた 今は見えなくなった
The time I spent with you was visible, but now it's out of sight.
透明な水星はぼんやりと でもそれだけ探してる
A transparent comet is faint, yet that's all I'm searching for.
四六時中を歌ったよ その時だけのメロディを
I sang around the clock, with a melody just for that moment.
寂しくなくなれなかったよ ちゃんと寂しく慣れたから
I couldn't stop feeling lonely, but I've finally gotten used to being lonely.
え、いつまでのごまかしなんて 正常か異常かなんて
Ugh, how long can we keep up this deception, and is it normal or abnormal?
考える暇もないほど 歩くのは大変だ ああ
There's no time to think about it, walking is so hard, ah.
楽しい方がずっといいよ ごまかして笑っていくよ
It's always better to have fun, I'll gloss it over and keep smiling.
大丈夫だ あの痛みは忘れたって消えやしない
It's alright, that pain won't disappear just because you forget it.
理想で作った道を 現実が塗り替えてくよ
Reality repaints the path we made with ideals.
思い出はその奇跡の上で 輝きになって残ってる
Memories remain, turned into brilliance upon those miracles.
お別れしたのはなんで 何のためだったんだろうな
Why did we say goodbye, and what was it all for?
悲しい光が僕の影を 前に長く伸ばしてる
A sorrowful light stretches my shadow far ahead.
抱きしめ合いつながってるよ 時間がある時に眠るよ
We're hugging and connected, I'll sleep when I have time.
夢だとはわかるその中で 君と会ってからまた行こう
I know it's a dream, within it, let's meet you and go again.
聖戦とはほど遠い 終わらない暗闇にも
Far from a holy war, even in the endless darkness,
星を思い浮かべたなら すぐ銀河の中だ ああ
if you picture the stars, you're right in the galaxy, ah.
甘えがなくなくなっても 靴を新しくしても
Even if my spoiling nature is gone, even if I get new shoes,
大丈夫だ あの痛みは忘れたって消えやしない
it's alright, that pain won't disappear just because you forget it.
伝えたかった言葉 きっとあったんだろうな
There must have been words I wanted to convey.
おそらくありふれたりなんだろうけど こんなにも
They're probably just common words, but even so...
お別れしたことは 出会ったことと繋がっている
Saying goodbye is connected to the fact that we met.
あの透明な水星は 透明だからなくならない
That transparent comet won't disappear because it's transparent.
丸バツ三角どれかなんて みんなと比べてどうかなんて
Comparing myself to everyone, wondering if I'm a circle, cross, or triangle,
確かめる間もないほど 生きるのは最高だ ああ
there's no time to check, living is the best, ah.
甘えがなくなくなっても ごまかして笑っていくよ
Even if my spoiling nature is gone, I'll gloss it over and keep smiling.
大丈夫だ あの痛みは忘れたって消えやしない
It's alright, that pain won't disappear just because you forget it.
大丈夫だ この光の始まりには
It's alright, at the beginning of this light,
君がいる
you are there.
この世界 迷い 誰かがみている
Wandering in this world, someone is watching—
心の中のケージ 変わってるイメージ
a cage in my heart, a shifting image,
固まったフェイス しいへさがすレース
a frozen face, a race searching for answers,
秘めとじこめたケース 君の描いた初め
a case kept hidden away, and the beginning you drew.
ねぇ 夢を見るのはいつ以来
Hey, how long has it been since I last dreamed?
ふいに始まる噛み芝居
A farce suddenly begins to play.
ここを出るにはどれくらい?
How long will it take to get out of here?
0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
ねぇ 夢を見るのはいつ以来
Hey, how long has it been since I last dreamed?
ふいに始まる意味したい
A meaningful farce suddenly begins to play.
ここを出るにはどれくらい?
How long will it take to get out of here?
0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
ねぇ 夢を見るのはいつ以来
Hey, how long has it been since I last dreamed?
心の中のケージ 変わってるイメージ
A cage in my heart, a shifting image,
固まったフェイス しいへさがすレース
a frozen face, a race searching for answers,
秘めとじこめたケース 君の描いた初め
a case kept hidden away, and the beginning you drew.
ねぇ 夢を見るのはいつ以来
Hey, how long has it been since I last dreamed?
ふいに始まる噛み芝居
A farce suddenly begins to play.
ここを出るにはどれくらい?
How long will it take to get out of here?
0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
出口のなさゼット
A dead-end 'Z',
足こもりリセット
resetting my tired feet,
迷い込むメイズ
wandering into a maze.
進めどもダルセーニョ
Moving forward, yet Dal Segno...
ドアの先に僕の背中が見えた
Ahead of the door, I saw my own back,
振り向いた先に希望を噛み締めた
and when I turned around, I embraced hope.
深国の果てなどどこにあるのか
Where is the end of the deep realm?
出口はまだなのか
Is there still no exit?
くるくるくるくる繰り返す 繰り返す 繰り返す 繰り返す
Round and round, repeating, repeating, repeating, repeating...
ふらふらふらふらふらくたる ふらくたる ふらくたる ふらくたる
Staggering, staggering, fractal, fractal, fractal, fractal...
たまわるさと
Rotating around,
終わらないロード
an endless road.
てつこさいさんそ
Iron-clad oxygen,
届かないSOS
an SOS that won't reach.
押してたザクロで梅雨はしのいだ
Pressing the pomegranate, I endured the rainy season,
巣がいのなかから雷が刺す
and lightning strikes from within the nest.
進めど進めど変わりないなら
If advancing brings no change at all...
泣き叫んで街を出る
Crying out as I leave the town,
同じ目差に肩寄せる
leaning shoulder to shoulder with the same gaze.
くるくるくるくるくりかえす
Round and round, over and over,
くりかえすくりかえすくりかえす
repeating, repeating, repeating.
ふらふらふらふらふらくたる
Wobbling, swaying, fractal,
ああ 扉を開け
Ah, open the door,
意味も忘れ
forgetting the meaning,
惹かれた夢の奥へ
deep into the captivating dream.
どこまでも続いてく
continuing on endlessly.
くるくるくるくるくりかえす
Spin, spin, round and round again.
(間奏)
(Instrumental Music)
さあ魂魂で剥がして縛り付けて
Come on, strip and bind the soul,
魂かわして てんぺんちでさらば
swap souls, goodbye in the upheaval.
憂きなし話して 楽しいね
Talk of woes, how fun it is.
期待込めてずっと 列をなすか ボッセいもた
Full of expectations, forming a line, bossy too.
一国も早くも心中 逆らいたい未来 閉ざされた欲の隅っこを果てば
Seeking a double suicide at the earliest, a future to rebel against, reaching the end of closed-off desires.
愛のりになってダンスミュージック
Riding on love, it's dance music.
パラノイアック 生き急いで 夢に見せられて 狂った世界 思い思い又マッスルビ
Paranoid, living in a rush, captivated by dreams, in a mad world, muscle beat.
蜂の巣回る 生き急いで 夢に見せられて
Spinning like a beehive, living in a rush, captivated by dreams.
ああ 今夜は 僕らは 夜迷いごとばかりだ
Ah, tonight we are all about night wanderings.
信じる貝殻の中 知らぬ老いたる心臓に頼る
In the shell of belief, relying on an unknown aged heart.
何度も何度も 懲りずに恋い慕いまして ハートビート 繰り返すもっと 生き急いで
Over and over, hopelessly pining away, heartbeat repeated, living in an even greater rush.
(間奏)
(Instrumental Music)
さあ魂魂で馬鹿みて 語り付けて
Come on, acting foolish with souls, talking on and on,
魂なくして 生生流転でさらば
losing the soul, goodbye in the flux of life.
まだ話して 話して 哀しいね
Keep talking, talking, how sad.
期待外れで意志を否定して こっちにおいで おいで おいで おいで
Disappointed and denying will, come over here, come here, come here, come here.
踏み出しても明日明日のまま はみ出しても貝は貝のまま 当然の帰結が流転の不滅笑い
Even if you step forward, tomorrow remains tomorrow; even if you stand out, a shell is a shell, an inevitable conclusion of flowing immortality's laugh.
一国も早くも心中 あなたに会いたい 枯れた夢の続きを愛して暮れるなら
Seeking a double suicide at the earliest, wanting to see you, if you will cherish the continuation of a withered dream.
一国も早くも心中 抗いたい未来 欠けた心の隙間を埋めれるなら
Seeking a double suicide at the earliest, a future to fight against, if you can fill the gap of a fractured heart.
(間奏)
(Instrumental Music)
のりになりなったダンスミュージック
Riding on, it became dance music.
パラノイアック 生き急いで 夢に見せられて 狂った世界 思い思い又マッスルビ
Paranoid, living in a rush, captivated by dreams, in a mad world, muscle beat.
蜂の巣回る 生き急いで 夢に見せられて
Spinning like a beehive, living in a rush, captivated by dreams.
ああ 今夜は ブラフマンに
Ah, tonight to Brahman,
パラノイアック 生き急いで 夢に見せられて 狂った世界 思い思い又マッスルビ
paranoid, living in a rush, captivated by dreams, in a mad world, muscle beat.
蜂の巣回る 生き急いで 夢に見せられて
Spinning like a beehive, living in a rush, captivated by dreams.
ああ 僕らは 僕らは 夜迷いごとなかだ
Ah, we are all about night wanderings.
信じる貝殻の中 知らぬ老いたる心臓に頼る
In the shell of belief, relying on an unknown aged heart.
何度も何度も 懲りずに恋い慕いまして ハートビート 繰り返すもっと せいせい流転で
Over and over, hopelessly pining away, heartbeat repeated, living in an even greater rush in the flux of life.
告々とせいせい流転で
Steadily and continuously in the flux of life.
(間奏)
(Instrumental Music)
ここはきっと夢の中ね
This is surely inside a dream.
(間奏)
(Instrumental Music)
目覚めたのは嘘みたいだ
Waking up feels like a lie.
知らないはずの部屋 振り返れば いくつもの目が
A room I shouldn't know. If I look back, countless eyes...
私を見つめていました
were staring right at me.
目指したのは温かかった
What I aimed for was warm,
私がいるはずの場所
the place where I ought to be.
目の前にはただ広がる まるで心の中みたいな
Spreading out before my eyes, just like inside my heart.
コンコンコンと扉の先 繰り返すループ 魂ためた音
Knock, knock, knock beyond the door, a repeating loop, sound of accumulated souls.
コンコンコンと笑い声 狐の少女が手招いてた
Knock, knock, knock and laughter, a fox girl beckoning.
ああ どうかそのまま
Ah, please stay just as you are.
この気持ちのエンドまで
To the end of these feelings,
連れて行って 連れて行って
take me away, take me away.
逃げ出したいよ
I want to run away,
抜け出したいから
because I want to escape.
いくつも扉開けた
I opened countless doors.
逃げ出したいよ
I want to run away,
抜け出したいのに
even though I want to escape.
わからない かわらない わからないな
I don't know, nothing changes, I don't know...
ここはきっと夢の中ね
This must be inside a dream.
寂しくひとり歩いてました
I was walking alone, feeling lonely.
戻ろうとしたら怒られました
When I tried to go back, I was scolded.
大事なことを忘れました
I forgot something important.
「出口はこちら」と言われました
I was told, "The exit is this way."
おかしな部屋に入りました
I entered a strange room.
仕方ないので進みました
Having no choice, I moved forward.
疲れたけど また見たのは
Though I was tired, what I saw again
知らないはずの部屋だった
was a room I shouldn't have known.
コンコンコンと扉の向こう
Knock, knock, knock, beyond the door,
終わらないループ ため息つき
an endless loop, letting out a sigh.
コンコンコンと笑う声
Knock, knock, knock, a laughing voice.
狐の少女は前を言った
The fox girl spoke ahead.
ああ 早くこのまま この迷路のエンドまで
Ah, hurry, just like this, to the end of this maze,
連れて行って おねがい
take me away, please.
逃げ出したいよ
I want to run away,
抜け出したいから
because I want to escape.
辿り着く と信じて
Believing I will reach it,
逃げ出したいよ
I want to run away,
抜け出したいよ
I want to escape.
わからない かわらない わからない
I don't know, nothing changes, I don't know,
わからない
I don't know.
逃げ出したいよ
I want to run away,
抜け出したいから
because I want to escape.
見つけた光はそこに
The light I found is right there.
逃げ出したんだ 逃げ出したんだ
I ran away, I ran away.
少女は静かに微笑んでた
The girl was smiling quietly.
ここがきっと夢の終わり
This must be the end of the dream.
最後の扉
The final door.
目の前には嘘みたいな
Right before my eyes, like a lie,
知らないはずの部屋
was a room I shouldn't have known.
振り返れば 少女は消えた
When I looked back, the girl had vanished.
私ずっと夢の中ね
I've been inside a dream all along.
皆さんこんばんは！王立図書館にて私、執筆しております。
Good evening, everyone! I am currently writing here at the Royal Library.
なんでも、先ほどのライブから自宅に帰って来ないスクンブがいるという噂が王国中に広がっているようだね。
Apparently, a rumor is spreading all over the kingdom that some Sukonbu hasn't returned home from the live performance just now.
まあ、この件に関しての解決はもしやすると、あの方々が動いてる可能性が……
Well, as for resolving this matter... could it be that those people are making a move...?
まあ、それは別のお話で。
Well, that's a story for another time.
では、ここからは私があご案内させていただきます！
Now, from here on, allow me to guide you!
まず1つ目、FOXXROOMアクリルジオラマスタンド！
First item: The FOXXROOM Acrylic Diorama Stand!
イラストはキューバメロ先生に描いていただきました。
The illustration was drawn by Cuba Melo-sensei.
この世界へつながる扉はあなたのすぐそばにあるのかもね。
The door connecting to this world might be right beside you.
続いては王国缶バッジ セイントver.です！
Next is the Kingdom Can Badge, Saint version!
キービジュアルを使用した缶バッジ。本体にホログラム加工とフレームデザインはジュエリー箔加工になっております。
A can badge using the key visual. The body features hologram processing and the frame design has jewelry foil processing.
この高級感、素敵ですよね！
This sense of luxury is wonderful, isn't it?
続いてはFBKINGDOM 騎士団法被！
Next is the FBKINGDOM Knights Happi coat!
王国騎士団員をイメージした法被です。デザインは国王様がデザインを、
This happi coat is inspired by the Royal Knights. The design was envisioned by His Majesty the King,
ブラッシュアップデザインをhyde先生が手掛けました。
and the polished design was handled by Hyde-sensei.
背中の騎士団ロゴ、そして裾のエンビ服がとても素敵ですよね！
The knights' logo on the back and the tail-coat hem are simply wonderful!
黒さんの部下の皆様は是非お手に！
All subordinates of Kuro-san, please make sure to get your hands on it!
続いてはすこん部ルームライトです！
Next is the Sukonbu Room Light!
LEDの色は2色あり、もちっとした素材を使用しております。
The LED has two colors, and it uses a squishy material.
インテリアとしても良し、温かい光に包まれてくださいね。
Great as interior decor, please let yourself be enveloped in its warm light.
フルセット購入特典としてチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
As a full-set purchase bonus, a cheki-style bromide card is included!
数量限定は直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入り、通常版は箔押し複製メッセージ入りです！
The limited quantity version includes a handwritten signature and foil-stamped duplicated message, and the regular version includes a foil-stamped duplicated message!
王国民の皆様はグッズサイトのご確認をよろしくお願いいたします。
All citizens of the kingdom, please check the merchandise site.
先ほどのセイントライブにてお披露
Unveiled at the Saint Live just a moment ago...
お待たせ！ 新曲
Kept you waiting! A new song,
『FOXXX ROOM』が10月6日24時にリリースされます！
Foxxx Room releases Oct 6 at 24:00!
さらに、この後22時30分より『FOXXX ROOM』のMVも公開予定！
Plus, Foxxx Room MV premieres at 22:30!
何気なく過ごす日常の隣にある世界をぜひお楽しみください！
Enjoy this world beside everyday life!
続いてはこちらをご覧ください！
Next, please take a look at this!
いいか、よく聞け！みろくの里をフブキングダムの領土とする！
Listen up! Miroku no Sato is ours!
よし、ここに王の証を残してやる！
Alright, I'll leave the king's mark here!
ここには等身大パネルも！
There are even life-sized panels!
みんなよ、この絶景！これが全部白神たちのものなんだぜ！
Look at this view! It's all Shirakami's!
みろくの里とフブキングダムはずっ友だよ！
Miroku no Sato & Fubuki Kingdom are besties!
はーい！ということで、フブキングダムの里いよいよ10月10日よりオープンです！
Fubuki Kingdom village opens October 10!
今流したホログラは10月11日から放送予定！ぜひ全編見に来てみてください！
HoloGra airs Oct 11! Watch the full version!
いやーフブキングダムが、ついに外に飛び出していくなんて、嬉しいですね〜！
So happy Fubuki Kingdom is venturing out!
ボイススタンプラリー、広島巡礼マップを確認してね。
Check the voice stamp rally & Hiroshima map.
スペシャルミニライブ、ここでしか聴けない曲もある、前編撮り下ろしのライブ！
Special mini-live with brand new footage!
コラボ限定グッズ、広島すんごんぬいぐるみをはじめとする可愛いグッズの数々など、現地にはお楽しみのコンテンツがもりだくさん！
Lots of fun goods like the Sungon plushie!
またメッセージボードも設置してもらいまーーす！必ず帰国報告をしてくださいね。
There's also a message board! Report back!
開催期間は11月3日までです！みなさんの帰国待ってますよー！
Event runs till Nov 3! We await your return!
ああ？カード？いやだよ、めんどくせぇ。
Huh? Cards? No way, that's too much work.
フブキングダムとホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームとのコラボが決定です！
Fubuki Kingdom x Hololive Card Game collab!
最後のは…難しくてもなんだかんだの人は…と、今後の情報にご期待です！告知は以上です！
Look forward to future updates! That's all!
では皆さん、またどこかでお会いしましょう！
See you all again somewhere soon!